atomicobject.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy | Atomic Object

This Privacy Policy applies atomicobject.com, spin.atomicobject.com, atomobj.io, and greatnotbig.com (and the associated social media accounts/pages), all of which are owned and operated by Atomic Object LLC (the “Site(s)”). This Privacy Policy describes how Atomic Object LLC (“we” or “us”) collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide in relation to the Sites only and does not represent all privacy practices conducted by us in our business. It describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information.

The use of information collected through the Sites shall be limited to the purposes of: (i) providing a service to you and other Users of the Sites (“Users”); (ii) the purpose for which you signed up to receive communications from us; and/or (iii) understanding companies and organizations interested in working with us. If you do not want your personal information to be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy, please do not use these Sites.

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

#### Personal Information

Information that could be used to identify or contact you is considered “Personal Information” under this Privacy Policy. Personal Information may include things such as first and last name, contact information, email address, physical address, and contents of your communication. Whether we collect Personal Information from you depends on how you use our Sites. Generally, when using our Sites, we may collect Personal Information in three ways: (i) you provide it to us through an inquiry, or (ii) you provide it to us through comments on our blog or social media, or (iii) you provide it to us when subscribing to blog post comments, or blog post feeds. Within the United States of America, we may additionally collect Personal Information from certain social media profiles.

We may use your information, including your Personal Information, for the following purposes:

  * To better understand how Users access and use our Sites, both on an aggregated and individual User basis, on individual Sites and across them in order to improve our Sites and respond to User desires and preferences, and for other research and analytical purposes;
  * To better understand companies and organizations interested in our services;
  * To provide services to you, which may include responding to your inquiries and troubleshooting problems;
  * For marketing and promotional purposes, including, for example, to send you notifications of new blog posts, or to otherwise contact you about projects or information we think may interest you provided you have opted into receiving such communications from us; and
  * To protect our own rights and interests, such as to resolve any disputes, enforce our Terms of Use, and to respond to legal requests.

We only collect the minimum amount of Personal Information about you that we consider necessary for achieving the aforementioned purposes. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other Users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

If you submit any Personal Information to us in response to a job posting (e.g. your resume), this may be shared with third parties (including external tools and services we use to manage our talent pool), depending on the nature of your inquiry. Personal Information collected in this capacity will be used solely for the purpose specified; such information is not subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

#### Non-Identifying Information

Certain information that does not identify you (“Non-Identifying Information”) would only be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (e.g., combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other Non-Identifying Information (e.g., your country and gender). We may combine your Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with Non-Identifying Information collected from other Users of the Sites to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Sites, and to analyze and understand how the Sites are used.

In general, we will gather some Non-Identifying Information automatically. This information includes your Internet service provider (“ISP”), device type, browser type, browser language and regional settings, geographic region, referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our Site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream. We gather this information using third-party services including Google Analytics, Chartbeat, and HotJar for monitoring website performance and determining customer service and Site needs. Please visit the privacy policies of these third parties to learn about their privacy practices and your opt-out choices.

Within the United States of America, we may gather some Non-Identifying Information from social media profiles if you have not opted-out of sharing such information through the associated social media service. We use this information to better understand companies interested in our services.

#### Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies

When you visit the Sites, we and our partners may use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the Sites, track Users’ movements around the Sites, and gather demographic information about our User base as a whole. Our Sites use cookies to distinguish you from other Users of our Sites. This helps us to provide you with a positive experience when you browse our Sites and allows us to improve our Sites and services.

You can choose to disable cookies. Disabling cookies may limit your use of certain features or functions on our Sites or services. If you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by any website, including these Sites, you should do this through each individual browser setting and on each device you use to access the Internet.

#### Log Data

When you visit the Sites, we automatically track certain information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Sites. This information may include the URL that you just came from, which URL you go to next, access times and dates, your computer browser information, your IP address, and other statistics (“Log Data”). We use Log Data for the Sites’ technical administration, to increase our Sites’ functionality and User-friendliness, and to better tailor the Sites to our Users’ needs. We also use the information to verify that the visitors to our Sites meet the criteria to process their requests. We do not combine log data with any other information that we may collect.

#### Do-Not-Track

Currently, our systems do not recognize browser “do-not-track” requests. You may, however, disable certain tracking as discussed in this section (e.g., by disabling cookies); you also may opt out of Internet-based advertising by following the instructions above in this Cookies section.

#### Regarding Children and Minors

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from Users under the age of 13 (“Child” or “Children”). If we learn that a Child’s Personal Information has been collected, we will delete the information. If parents or guardians believe that we have unintentionally collected their Child’s Personal Information, they should contact us to request the deletion of the information at privacy@atomicobject.com.

### Disclosure of Your Information

#### Other Corporate Entities

We may share your information, including your Personal Information, Non-Identifying Information and Log Data, with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. We do not share your information with any entities that are not part of our business activities. We do not sell your email address or contact information with any third parties.

#### Legal Requests

We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws and intellectual property rights. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement, we may disclose your Personal Information.

### Storage and Transfer of Your Information

Depending on the Site you are using, or how you contact us, your information is stored on the servers of our service providers. Please note that information we collect from you will be stored and processed in the United States.

### Security of Your Information

We use reasonable physical, procedural, technical and administrative security measures to protect your Personal Information against loss or theft – as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100 percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Your Personal Information Rights

We acknowledge that you have the right to access your Personal Information.

We may retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. In certain circumstances, we may be required by law to retain your Personal Information, or we may need to retain your Personal Information in order to continue providing a service.

Users may request the removal of content or information they have posted publicly on the Site. Please be advised that any information you post to a bulletin board, message board, chat room, community, or other forum is publicly viewable. We strongly recommend that all Users avoid posting personal or sensitive information at any time.

Please note that removal of this content or information from public view does not guarantee complete or comprehensive removal. After your removal request has been honored, we may retain copies of the content or information you have previously posted on our servers (e.g., in backups). Additionally, we do not have control over third parties (e.g., other Users) who may have copied or reposted this information.

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your Personal Information by contacting us at privacy@atomicobject. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe in accordance with applicable law.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The most up-to-date version of this Privacy Policy will be published to the Sites, which you are advised to consult regularly for any changes. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.

### Contact Us

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this Site or at: Atomic Object, c/o Privacy Officer, 1034 Wealthy St SE, Grand Rapids, MI, 49506, USA, (616) 776-6020, [privacy@atomicobject.](mailto:privacynotice@ideo.com)

### Subscriptions and Communications to You

We invite Users who are interested in hearing more about activities on the Sites to subscribe to notifications. By signing up to one of our subscriptions, you are giving consent to receive relevant emails and communications from us (“Subscription”). Your Subscription will allow us to contact you regarding the Sites. If you have previously signed up for a subscription and would like to unsubscribe, you may opt out of these communications at any time by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email or by emailing us at [privacy@atomicobject.com](mailto:privacy@atomicobject.com).
